question_data = [{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The retail disc of Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 5 only comes with the tutorial.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Vehicles","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In 1993 Swedish car manufacturer Saab experimented with replacing the steering wheel with a joystick in a Saab 9000.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In 'The Sims' series, the most members in a household you can have is 8.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Japan was part of the Allied Powers during World War I.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"This is the correct spelling of 'Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious'.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The Kingdom of Prussia briefly held land in Estonia.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Unturned originally started as a Roblox game.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Joseph Stalin's real name was Ioseb Bessarionis dze Dzugashvili.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the comic book 'Archie', Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the game 'Melty Blood Actress Again Current Code', you can enter Blood Heat mode in Half Moon style.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The first 'Metal Gear' game was released for the PlayStation 1.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"'Number 16 Bus Shelter' was a child's name that was approved by the New Zealand government.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The fourth funnel of the RMS Titanic was fake designed to make the ship look more powerful and symmetrical.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In Undertale, having a 'Fun Value' set to 56-57 will play the 'Wrong Number Song Call'.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"TF2: Sentry rocket damage falloff is calculated based on the distance between the sentry and the enemy, not the engineer and the enemy","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Mythology","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Rannamaari was a sea demon that haunted the people of the Maldives and had to be appeased monthly with the sacrifice of a virgin girl.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"DHCP stands for Dynamic Host Configuration Port.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The song 'Mystery Train' was released by artist 'Little Junior's Blue Flames' in 1953.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"'Cube', 'Cube 2: Hypercube' and 'Cube Zero' were directed by the same person.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The Battle of Trafalgar took place on October 23rd, 1805","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The names of Roxas's Keyblades in Kingdom Hearts are 'Oathkeeper' and 'Oblivion'.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Switzerland has four national languages, English being one of them.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The band STRFKR was also briefly known as Pyramiddd.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Books","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Harry Potter was born on July 31st, 1980.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"All of these maps were in 'Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Siege' on its initial release: House, Clubhouse, Border, Consulate.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The chemical element Lithium is named after the country of Lithuania.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The USS Missouri (BB-63) last served in the Korean War.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Druid is a mage class in 'Log Horizon'.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Television","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The Klingon home planet is Qo'noS.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Board Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The board game Go has more possible legal positions than the number of atoms in the visible universe.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Celebrities","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Lady Gaga's real name is Stefani Joanne Angelina Germanotta.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In Topology, the complement of an open set is a closed set.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The value of one Calorie is different than the value of one calorie.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"During the Winter War, the amount of Soviet Union soliders that died or went missing was five times more than Finland's.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The weapon Clint Eastwood uses in 'Dirty Harry' was a .44 Automag.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"L'H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Politics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"George Clinton, Vice President of the United States (1805-1812), is an ancestor of President Bill Clinton.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the 'To Love-Ru' series, Peke is considered a female robot.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The two largest ethnic groups of Belgium are Flemish and Walloon. ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the 'Kagerou Daze' series, Shintaro Kisaragi is prominently shown with the color red.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Mythology","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Janus was the Roman god of doorways and passageways.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The singer Billie Holiday was also known as 'Lady Day'.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The character Plum from 'No Game No Life' is a girl.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Vehicles","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The term 'GTO' was originated by Ferrari?","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The video game 'Fuel' has an open world that is 5,560 square miles?","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Only one country in the world starts with the letter Q.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"YouTube personality Jenna Marbles served as an executive producer of the film Maximum Ride (2016).","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The T-Mobile Sidekick smartphone is a re-branded version of the Danger Hiptop.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The Paradox Interactive game 'Stellaris' was released in 2016.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The protagonist's names in 'Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf', George and Martha, were derived from George Washington and his wife.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]